(Sheldon:)They took our TV, two laptops,
four external hard drives...
(Sheldon:)...our PS2, our PS3, our Xbox,
our Xbox 360, our classic Nintendo...
(Sheldon:)...our Super Nintendo,
our Nintendo 64, and our Wii.
(Leonard:)We like games.
Right, games. They took "Halo 1," "Halo 2,"
"Halo 3," "Call of Duty 1," "Call of Duty 2"...
..."Call of Duty 3," "Rock Band"...
..."Final Fantasy I" through "IX,"
"The Legend of Zelda: Ocarina of Time"...
..."The Legend of Zelda: Twilight Princess,"
"Super Mario Bros."...
..."Mario & Sonic
at the Winter Olympics"...
...and "Ms. Pac-Man."
(Policeman:)Assorted video games.
(Sheldon:)When does the CSI team get here?
(Leonard:)-What?
-In anticipation of their arrival...
(Sheldon:)...I've bagged some evidence.
(Sheldon:)One of the thieves had the audacity
to quench his thirst...
(Sheldon:)...while ransacking our home.
You should be able to pull prints off this.
(Sheldon:)Here are my prints
so you can rule me out as a suspect.